forebet.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy

| 

This privacy policy sets out how Forebet.com uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

We respect your personal information and are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.

You should check this page for updates whenever you would like to ensure that you agree with any changes. This policy was last updated 20 May 2018.

**What we collect**

If you choose to register at our website we collect the following data, which you input in the registration form:

  * Name
  * Username
  * E-mail address
  * Country

We may collect some personally identifiable information, including Android Advertising Id, Device IDs or unique identifiers, iOs Advertising Identifier in order to improve user experience, while using our service.

**How and why we collect data**

We collect the data specified above in case that you choose to register at our website through our registration form to create your account. We only ask for information that is necessary to enable each web site user to use this web site satisfactorily and improve user experience.

Your Name and E-mail are securely stored in our server. If you have agreed to receive emails  from us, we may use them to send you email messages like news about our website or other information, which we think you might find interesting.

We use your Country information to try to present you the correct time for each sport event according to your location and timezone, as well as set your correct language preferences.

The Username which you have chosen is used when you log in to our website.

Our apps may store some unique identifiers of your device for analytics purposes and for storing your preferences.

**  
Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We use variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Our website uses HTTPS (connection security). We do not share your personal information with third parties.

**  
Controlling your personal information**

You have full control over the information that you have entered when you registered on our website. You can access it, require it being edited or entirely delete it from our servers.

  * **Access your data on our servers**  
You can access all the data we have stored on our servers at your profile page, when you have logged in at the website.
  * **Delete your data from our servers**  
If you choose to delete your profile and all information associated with it you can make such a request at [privacy@forebet.com](mailto:privacy@forebet.com) and you will be informed shortly after your data has been deleted from our servers.
  * **Edit your data**  
If you want us to make changes on your profile data you can make a request at [privacy@forebet.com](mailto:privacy@forebet.com) and you will be informed shortly after the changes are commited.
  * **Opt-out of our newsletter**  
You can opt-out of our newsletter by following the instruction on the last received email from us or simply email us at [privacy@forebet.com](mailto:privacy@forebet.com) to be removed from our newsletter.

**  
Cookies**

You should be aware that when you use our websites, mobile sites, or mobile apps, we may collect information by using 'cookies'.

  * **What are cookies and how do they work?  
** Cookies are small bits of text that are downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Your browser sends these cookies back to the website every time you visit the site again, so it can recognise you and can then tailor what you see on the screen.
  * **What do you use cookies for?**  
Cookies are an important part of the Internet. They make using websites much smoother and affect lots of the useful features of websites.

Some cookies are essential to provide you the service of the website and use its features like: 

    * Keeping you logged in during your visit.
    * Maintaining your session and navigating through the website smoothly.
    * Improving your browsing experience: 
      * These cookies allow the website to remember your settings, such as your language, your time zone or odds presentation (decimal or fractional) and provide you improved features.
  * **Third-Party Cookie  
** Each cookie is associated with a domain, which refers to the website that places the cookie. On our website there are third-party cookies that are placed by other applications and help analytics and advertising on the website.

Third-Party Cookies at our website might be set by Google Analytics, Google Adsense, Google AdMob, DoubleClick, Facebook, Twitter, Criteo or their partner networks.

You can choose to accept or reject the use of cookies. Usually, the web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you should be able to reject cookies from your browser’s settings. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of all the website features.

If you wish to turn off only third party cookies, which are used for personalized ads please visit (Your Online Choices site. ) <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/>

**Advertisement**

The content available at Forebet.com is free and has always been free. We work very hard to deliver you high quality service, but we want to keep it free of any charge.

Therefore, we use advertisements. The ads that appear on our website may be set by the advertising networks Google AdSense, Criteo or their partner networks. On our android Forebet app the ads are set by Google AdMob.

These platforms can set cookies (third party cookies) in order to deliver you personalized ads.

The personalized ads are delivered through the use of variety of sophisticated methods, which work with some of your data, to try to present you ads that might be more relevant to you. If you choose not to be shown personalized ads you can always reject cookies on your browser.

For more information on how Google products that we use (Google Adsense, Google Analytics, DoubleClick) can use your information, please visit <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

**  
Other information we collect**

  * **Social media widgets  
** On our website there are some social media features, such as the Facebook Like button,  Google+ +1 Button and Twitter Follow Button. These features may collect some information about you such as your IP address and which page you are visiting on our website, and may set additional cookie. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the organization providing it.
  * **Email tracking**  
On some of the emails we send we put in tracking so that we can tell how much traffic those emails send to our site and we can track, at an individual level, whether the user has opened and clicked on the email.

**Links to other websites**

At our website there might be some links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website and cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites.

For more information, please also check our [Terms of use](https://www.forebet.com/en/terms-of-use).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of our website, please contact us at [privacy@forebet.com](mailto:privacy@forebet.com)

|   
---|---|---
